#### Contact

5164480889 (Home) kmd147@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/katherine-dillon-3b7303a3 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing
Nursing Management
Nursing Process

## Languages

Spanish

#### Certifications

Basic Life Support (BLS)

**PALS** 

ACLS

Honors-Awards

Dean's List

# Katherine Dillon

**BSN RN CWOCN** 

Nashville

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Patient Advocacy, Patient Education, and Critical Thinking. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing (B.S.N) from New York University and Wound, Ostomy, Continence certified from Emory University.

## Experience

Saint Thomas Health 4 years 9 months

Wound, Ostomy, and Continence Nurse January 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months) Nashville, TN, United States

## Charge Nurse

July 2017 - July 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Nashville, Tennessee

Cardiac Catheterization Lab Charge RN

#### Registered Nurse

December 2015 - July 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Cardiac Catheterization Lab

Vanderbilt University Medical Center Registered Nurse-Burn Nurse Resident January 2015 - December 2015 (1 year)

Nashville, Tennessee

**Burn Intensive Care Unit** 

Hospital for Special Surgery

2 years

Patient Care Assistant 2013 - 2015 (2 years) Nurse Extern June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

# Education

Emory University

CWOCN, Wound, Ostomy, Continence Nursing · (2018 - 2018)

New York University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2014)

University of Pittsburgh
Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2011)